# ason **Hannanto**

3001 Front St. Alhambra, CA 91803

© (626) 267-6038 | ■ Hannanto@usc.edu | 🏕 www.JasonHannanto.github.io | 🖸 JasonHannanto | 🛅 JasonHannanto

# Summary\_

Hi! My name is Jason. I'm currently a sophomore at the University of Southern California pursuing a B.S in Computer Science. Creating and perfecting a smooth and exciting user experience on a digital platform is my craft and I'm always excited to learn about new technologies to see how I better develop solutions. I know I have a long ways to go, as well as a lot to learn, which is why I am working hard everyday to achieve my dreams

# **Education**

#### **University Of Southern California**

Los Angeles, CA

INTENDED DEGREE: B.S. IN COMPUTER SCIENCE Expected Graduation: 2020

**Pasadena City College** 

Pasadena, CA

COMPUTER SCIENCE 2015-2017

# **Work Experience**

#### **Reliant Pulmonary/Critical Care**

Monterey Park, CA

Summers 2013-2015

MEDICAL SCRIBE

Mar. 2016 - Aug 2017

- · Complete realtime/retrospective charting of patient encounters, including History of Present Illness, Review of Systems, Past Medical History, Family/Social History, Assessment (ICD-10 coding)/Plan, Vitals, Diagnostic Tests, and Medications.
- Navigation/set-up of EHR/Radiographic Imaging software/programs
- Documentation/Transcription of Lab Results, Radiographic Imagery Reports, and procedural reports.

Bazic Products Inc. El Monte, CA

- · Management of freight delivery records using Microsoft Excel
- Manage Driver Logs/COD (Cash on Delivery)
- Fix item quantity discrepancies between warehouse and SAP

# **Projects**

ADMINISTRATIVE ASSISTANT

#### [Current] Music Lyric/Chord Management Web App

WEB APP ALLOWS USERS TO CREATE/STORE SONGS WITH CHORDS FOR LIVE PLAYING. FEATURES THE CAPABILITY TO TRANSPOSE

Aug 2017 - Present

- KEYS LIVE. USED WEEKLY BY THE CHURCH MUSIC TEAM. Working under a Senior Software Developer
- Debug posted issues / Refactor code for efficiency
- Develop new features for Web App

#### [Current] JasonHannanto.github.io

PORTFOLIO/RESUME WEBSITE · Creating a visually appealing and responsive website Aug 2017 - Present

#### Mp3 Player

PYTHON CONSOLE-BASED PROGRAM REPLICATING MP3 PLAYER

2017

· Create playlists, play songs, display information. Utilized OOP principles create Song/User Objects in a scalable matter.

### Skills

Frontend, HTML, CSS, Javascript, JQuery, Bootstrap

Backend, Node.js, Express.js

Database, NoSQL, MongoDB, Mongoose

Programming, C++, Python

Version Control, Git

Principles, REST, TDD, OPP, Unit Testing